Diversity and Inclusion, Office of; Records ua370
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Recruitment Plans, 1973-1985; 1.66 cubic ft.
  - Personnel Budgeting, SUNYA Minorities, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Black Faculty and Staff Lists and Requests, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Black Faculty and Staff Lists and Requests, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Publications, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - School Studies, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Noticiero, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - MAPP, Dollree F/01 Incarceration, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Minority Enrollment, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Minority Education, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Title IX, 1975-1978; 1.33 cubic ft.
  This series documents the implementation of the Title IX Program on the Albany Campus. It reveals the actions taken by what was known as the Affirmative Action Office at the time and its work with faculty and staff to amend hiring processes on campus and implement new sports programs. This includes studies and reports on what were current hiring processes and sports teams’ offerings, as well as information from other universities and colleges and their work with Title IX.
  - Women Faculty Higher Ed Court Battle Documentation, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Court Cases, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Speak Out: Feminist Journal, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Status of Women at SUNY Albany, 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Education of Women, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Title IX, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Title IX Self Evaluation, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Departmental Reports, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Women's Sports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Raffel, Norma, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Title IX Self Study: Draft1, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Studies/ Title 9 Report, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Title IX Graduate Student Report, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Inter Collegiate Athletics: Self Assessment, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Norma Raffel, Title IX Consultant, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Literature File Holdings, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Literature File Holdings A, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - SUNY Resource Guide, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 504 Concerns, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Articles on University and Disabled Students, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Athletics and Title IX, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Women's Sports Investigation, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Equipment Cages, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Title IX Amendments, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Where are the Women ? Title IX Self Study, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Title IX Self Study, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Title IX Articles, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Title IX, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Title IX Report, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Title IX Instructional Self Evaluation, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Grievance Procedure for Review, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Title IX Self Evaluation Procedure, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Title IX Articles and Policies, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Title IX Articles and Policies, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Curriculum Waivers, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Title IX Peer Publication, 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Section 504, 1977-1980; 1.33 cubic ft.
  Collection is arranged in its original order
  This series documents the Office of Diversity and Inclusion’s Implementation of new Section 504 guidelines, which prohibits discrimination of individuals based on a disability. In this series can be found results of self-studies of the University, reports from the 504 Task Force on success of the program, and future plans to amend employment and admissions practices on campus.
  - CUPA Conference Papers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 504 Fact Sheet, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Working Paper n Intercollegiate Athletics, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Athletics, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Coaching Staff Policies, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Schedule, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Game Programs, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 504 Task Force, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Facilitating Campus Accessibility, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Title IX, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - New Paltz, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 504 Smoking, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 504 S.S Design, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Handicapped Past Action, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 504 Task Force, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Academic Advisement, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Admissions, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Architectural Barriers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 504 Regulations, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 504 Reports, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Budget 504, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Employment 504, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 504 Workshop on Campus Access, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 504 Next Meeting, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 504 Accessibility/Education, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Sub C. 504 Publicity and Public Ed, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rehabilitation Services, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 504 Concerns, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 504 Concerns, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 504 Task Force, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 504 Task Force, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 504 Concerns Group, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 504 Concerns: Part 1, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Five Year Plan, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Coalition, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 504 Transition Plan, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 505 and Employment, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Service Rights, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 504 Concerns, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 504 Reports, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- General Subject Files, 1988-1998; 1.00 cubic ft.
  The General Subject Files holds a diverse array of materials that passed through the hands of the Office of Diversity and Inclusion. This includes campus handbooks and manuals from academic departments and extracurricular activities that needed approval from the office, and articles on issues addressed by the office like sexual harassment.
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounting Placement Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bahia de Ifa, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Systemic Psychology Lab Manual, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Technical Report Liquids, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A Celebration of Literacy, Student Writing, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Client Evaluation and Equipment Prescription, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sexual Harassment: It's no Game, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Community and Public Service Program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Journals of Continuing Social Work Education, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Information for Applicants, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Disability Needs Assessment, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Handbook for Student Teaching Center, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - New Coordination Institute, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Employee Assistance Program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Department of Environmental Health and Toxicology, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation Conference, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Institute for Traffic Safety Management and Research, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Middle Earth Training Manual, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Department of Philosophy: Course Bulletin, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Internship Handbook, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Reports from Departments, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Physics 108 Lab Manual, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Physics Problem Solving, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Shining in the 90's, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Orientation Program on A10's, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - PDP: Staff Directory, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - VESC Orientation Manual, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - A New Constitution for a New Century, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - How to Work with Individuals and Groups, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Basic Guide to Living off campus, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Justically Speaking…, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Pathways to Professional Development, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Staff Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Questions and Answers: An Update on Disability Related Topics, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Educational Opportunities Program Newsletter, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Recruitment and Selection Policies, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Affirmative Action Office, 1977-2003; 2.83 cubic ft.
  Series was maintained in its original order.
  This series holds papers related to the span of time that the Office of Diversity and Inclusion was known as the Affirmative Action Office. This includes a variety of office based materials such as internal memos, correspondence, articles and reports on harassment, periodicals published and written by the office, and meeting minutes. All relates to the Office’s efforts to address racism, sexism, and general prejudice on campus. This series also includes materials related to Gloria DeSole, temporary Acting Director of the Office, before becoming Senior Advisor to the President for Affirmative Action and Employment Planning and still acting as head of The Affirmative Action Office. This included her work with the President’s Task force on Women’s Safety, Women’s Concerns Committee, and the LGB Concerns Committee.
  - Hokum Humor Magazines, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ASP Articles & Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Guidelines on Discrimination, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reverse Discrimination, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Grey Stevens Digest, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gloria DeSole Diversity Chairs Meeting, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Diversity Committees Memoranda, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Diversity Committees, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Diversity Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Diversity Committees, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Feminism, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Faussilte, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Hispanics, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NSACS Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Middle States, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Higher Education, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Papers Minorities, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minority Hiring, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - NCBI Training, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Peer Harassment, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Politically Correct, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CARR Post Doc, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Sexism, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sexist Language, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Sexual and Racial Harassment, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stop Violence Against Women, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Workshop Information, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Empowerment Project, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Contract Information Empowerment Project, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Budgets, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Calendar, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Leaders of Womens Groups, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Womens Meeting with President, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Womens Meeting with President, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Womens Meeting with President, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Womens Meeting with President, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Womens Meeting with President, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Womens Connection, 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Womens Connection, 1979-1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Womens Connection, 1994-2001 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - The Advocate, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Age Discrimination, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - AIDS, 1992; 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Update, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Women, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Albany Plan, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Albany Plan, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Albany Plan, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Albany Plan, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Albany Plan, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Albany Plan, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Management Association, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bakke Decision, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Community Foundation, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Focus, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Racism, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Racial Concerns Across the Campus, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Sexual Harassment Pamphlets, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Harassment Advisors, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sexual Harassment Advising, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - H Advisors, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Sexual Harassment Advisors, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Statistics Affirmative Action, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Womens Concerns Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Annual Report and Grievance Procedure, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Disabilities Report, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - University Commission for Affirmative Action, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Public Service, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Battle John F, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - LGB Concerns Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Safety Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Safety Task Force, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Safety Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Safety Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Womens Safety, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Womens Safety, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Womens Safety, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Womens Safety, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Presidents Committee on Women in 80's, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Womens Safety Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Black Advisory, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Black Advisor board, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Black Caucus Structure, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Black Caucus SUNY Affirmative Action Policies and Implementation, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Black Studies, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Black Care at University at Albany, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Student, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Safety News Articles, 1974-1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Womens Safety Crimes Against Women, 1978-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Womens Safety Committee, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - On Campus Articles Posters, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Vetter Chrov Art and Science, 1972-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Womens Safety - Self Defense Workshop Vouchers for Maggie Beso, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Womens Safety Protecting Yourself Articles, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action Offices, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Where are the Women ?" - Title IX Self-Study, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Women's Studies 399: Classism, Racism, and Sexism, 1977; 0.5 cubic ft.
  Collection is arranged in its original order.
  The collection holds the materials from Women's Studies Class 399: Classism, Racism, and Sexism. It was taught by Gloria DeSole who was the Director of the Affirmative Action Office. Materials include; student lists, syllabi, handouts, and DeSole's class notes for lecture.
  - Collected Articles, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Collected Articles, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Collected Articles, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Classism, Racism and Sexism Course Info, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class Article List, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Other Class Articles, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Info, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minority Concerns, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Minority Women, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Women, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Office of Diversity and Inclusion Files, 2015; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have been arrange chronologically.
  This series holds files documenting the span of time since the Office of Diversity and Inclusion began operating under its current name. This series includes affirmative action plans for both organizations within the university and the university as a whole.
  - 2015 Affirmative Action Plan for the Research Foundation (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University Affirmative Action Plan, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Research Foundation Affirmative Action Plans, 1984-1996; 1 cubic ft.
  Files in this series were maintained in their original order upon processing.
  This series contains yearly plans produced by the Research Foundation, describing ways in which the foundation is committed to diversity and outlining nondiscrimination policies to be put in place. This series also includes workforce analysis reports with ethnic and gender breakdowns of various offices and departments within the university.
  - Central Office Plan Update, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AA Plan CEN OFF, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Research Foundation Affirmative Action Plan for 1985 Support Files (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Research Foundation Affirmative Action Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation Appendices, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation Audit Files, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation [1 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation [2 of 2], 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Plan Part 2 Draft, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for the Research Foundation Part 2, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Workforce Analysis Report Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for the Research Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for the Research Foundation Part 2, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Workforce Analysis Report, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for Research Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Affirmative Action Plan for the Research Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Work Force Analysis Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)